# JUAN FELIPE PRECIADO ALVAREZ

Mail: juan.preciado@gmail.com

Phone nr: +45 23 36 49 19 Website: juanpreciado.co

Hometown: Medellín, Colombia

Current residence: Odense, Denmark

Birthday: 1989.02.16

Passport nr: AO986181

CPR number: 160289-4203

Languages: Spanish (Native)

English (Bilingual)
Danish (Basic)



I have an academic background in Computer Science, graduated in 2012 from Universidad Nacional de Colombia, in Medellín, but I have been working in software development since 2011, mostly focused on web. In 2014 I took the decision to gained some international experience so I left my beloved Colombia and started a new adventure in Denmark.

I have been working full time in different companies, mostly on technology products, related with web applications, using Java or PHP (Depending of the company and the product) for the backend part, and frontend technologies like jQuery, SASS/SCSS, LessCSS and HTML5.

## Programming languages and skills

Java, jQuery, PHP, CSS/CSS3, SASS/SCSS, LessCSS, JavaScript, SQL, XML, JavaServer Faces, XQuery, Scrum, MySQL, HTML/HTML5, PostgreSQL, Hibernate, JBoss Drools, SugarCRM just to mention some of the technologies I have worked with, and I am also willing always to learn about new technologies and tools.

### **Experience**

### Jysk Fynske Medier

Odense, Denmark. April 2014 - Now

I am responsible for the building and the maintenance (both back-end and front-end) of several media houses' sites, all of them them run on an in-house developed CMS for which I am also part of the team which implements new features to it. Tasks include making existing websites responsive or adaptative according to the needs, as well as implementing new features for the backend part. Some of the sites I have work with inlcude: TV2OJ.dk, Fyens.dk, Mitfyn.dk,Folketidende.dk, SN.dk, JV.dk to mention but a few. Technologies used: PHP, Smarty, jQuery, MySQL, LessCSS, SASS/SCSS, MySQL, GIT

#### Enlace Operativo Compuredes

Medellín, Colombia. March 2013 - March 2014

I worked as JAVA devoleper, in the building and maintenance of a web app called SuAporte, which was use for payment of Social Security in Colombia, responsabilities includes both, frontend and backend development Technologies used: JAVA/J2EE, Java Server Faces, jQuery, Oracle, JBoss Drools, SVN

#### Yuxi Pacific

Medellín, Colombia. August 2012 - March 2013

I work as technician leader for the MSI project, an in-house CMS build with an XML database, used to manage reviews of critics about books, magazines, and media material (DVDs, Video games, etc.)

Technologies used: Java, jQuery, Marklogic (A XML database and Application server engine), XQuery (A query language for XML), SVN

## **Education**

### Universidad Nacional de Colombia, sede Medellín

Medellín, Colombia. Graduated in March 2012

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering and Information Technologies